<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">PowerTutor2</string>
    <string name="running_on_startup">The Power Profiler will now run after your phone starts up.</string>
    <string name="not_running_on_startup">The Power Profiler will no longer run on when your phone starts up.</string>
    <string name="stop_sending_text"></string>
    <string name="start_sending_text"></string>
    <string name="unknown_phone">Your phone type is not recognized by PowerTutor2. You may continue to use PowerTutor2 however we may not be able to get all of the data for your phone and the power calculations may not be accurate.</string>
    <string name="term"></string>
    <string name="help_head"><big><b>PowerTutor2</b></big> - A real-time system and application power monitor.</string>
    <string name="help_text">\n<ul><li><b>Main control panel</b>\n
     - Start/stop profiling services. \n
     - Select <b>Application</b> or <b>System</b> mode to check out power consumption statistics.\n
     - Menu features:\n
        \t* Enable/Disable the profiling service to run on startup.\n
        \t* Save the current power trace to the sdcard.\n</li>\n<li><b>App View</b>\n
     - Displays power usage information for all of the apps running on the
           phone.\n
     - Press an app row to go to the <i>Graph View</i> for that app\'s power
           usage.\n
     - Press a hardware component name in the top tabs to include/exclude it from power
            calculations.\n
     - Data interpretation:\n
        \t* Percentage value: The percentage of energy/average power consumed by the 
            app in system.\n
        \t* Time value: Time that the app has been actively monitored by PowerTutor2.\n
     - Menu features:\n
        \t* Change the sort key to one of current power, average power, or total energy usage.\n
        \t* Change the time span to include the last minute, hour, day, or all time.\n</li>\n<li><b>Graph View</b>\n
     - Displays app/system power consumption decomposed by hardware component.\n
     - Use the tabs at the top to move between <i>Chart View</i> and <i>Pie
       View</i>.\n</li>\n<li><b>Chart View</b>\n
     - Displays the power usage of different components on the phone in recent
           history.\n
     - Scroll to view different component power graphs.\n
     - Menu features:\n
        \t* Select \"<i>Set History Size</i>\" to adjust the number of data points
           displayed.\n
        \t* Select \"<i>Magnify Recent Data</i>\" to show more recent data points
           more spread out.\n
        \t* Select \"<i>Pause</i>\" to freeze the display as is, select resume to
           continue.\n</li>\n<li><b>Pie View</b>\n
     - Displays the power usage percentages of the different components.\n
     - Menu features:\n
        \t* Change the time span to include the last minute, hour, day, or all time.\n</li>\n</ul></string>
<string name="url_1"></string>
<string name="url_2"></string>

</resources>